(2 people) Seino... (Sound of breathing)
(Igawa) Fu! (Mayumi) Yay
Congratulations (Mayumi) Congratulations
It's the 3rd anniversary, isn't it?
≪I was happy≫
What do you think? Does Piotr look good?
Peter? Yes, I just arrived.
what? You look like you like that name
(Mayumi) Eh? Look, Peter
Oh, look, I'm happy.
(Takako Mitsuru) Hello
“I walked 10,000 steps” feels better, right?
≪I thought the casual days would continue like this forever≫
Seno... (Sound of breathing)
≪One day, suddenly...≫
(Mayumi) Kya!
Peter... I...
Because I left the window open...
♬〜
Ah... ah...
Ah...
(Sawai) He was found without any ID or mobile phone...
Mayumi?
(cry)
(Mayumi) Hey, I was thinking...
why? Since when?
I was in the hospital for a week after the accident.
Which one are you?
What kind of joke are you kidding? It's Ikawa.
Igawa is me though
Someone else is pretending to be me
no one remembers me
So who am I? That's it
(Yuri) I'm sure your wife will be fine.
There's no way I'll forget someone important to me
≪Years and decades from now
Time that is supposed to accumulate...≫
Which one are you?
≪Disappeared≫
Mayumi...
hang on! (Mayumi) Please stop it.
Wait, Mayumi! hang on!
Please come out!
Mayumi Wait, wait!
please explain what you mean
(Mayumi) What are you talking about? Why are you pretending not to know?
who are you?
This is Masaki Igawa, your husband.
Huh? Is that wrong?
You celebrated your wedding anniversary the other day, right? June 19th
How do you know? There's no way you'll forget
Two days later Peter died.
What are you talking about? Peter is alive!
Mayumi turned into a stray cat because she left the window open...
Ah... it's not that the different Mayumi is bad...
Yes, Peter...
(Mayumi) Eh... what? what?
♬〜
What are you doing?
Peter here...
♬〜
why…
Please be careful, Peter is inside.
different! petr is dead
(Mayumi) Peter is alive! Peter is dead!
So what is Peter inside?
That's your new pet, right?
First of all, why...
How do you know about Peter?
It's obvious
I gave him the name Peter.
(cry)
♬〜
(Tada) What are you doing there?
What do you mean by barging into my house?
If you want to do something even weirder...
I'll make it impossible for you to sit down!
♬〜
I'm home (ji) Welcome back
Sorry I'm late
(Ji) Is Friday a visiting day? Yeah
It seems like they're going to do a jumping box in PE, so Uncle Osamu wants him to come and watch.
(Address) Oh Friday
The university is closed to commemorate its founding, so I'm going to go see it.
Yeah, I'm happy (ji) hahahaha
What?
Isn't there someone good? Huh?
(Osamu) No, even Kento can easily take care of his new father now...
Hey, I thought you might be accepted.
You know, it's like staying with your old relative forever, isn't it?
One of these days
(Osamu) Hmm... Are there no good people at work?
If you go to a prep school, you'll have a lot of encounters.
Most of the people I interact with are parents.
Ah... then what about that? The matching thing
Is everyone doing it now? What, do you know?
That's because young students are talking about it.
Ah, but is that so?
I don't know what he's like until I meet him, so it's dangerous.
Ah, no, I don't know if I met you.
Hehe, hehe, I recommend it. Is that it?
No, it's dangerous after all.
I'd like to introduce someone from the university, a good young researcher.
thank you
But right now I don't feel like that yet.
It's okay to be alone
Ah... I'll cause trouble for my uncle though.
(Osamu) No, no, no, I'm not like that...
If only Yuri could be happy
Thank you, I'll go
Yeah, then I'll see what time it is on Friday.
Please email me (fix)
Be careful ah
thank you
♬〜
Please help! (Watanabe) What happened?
Other people are pretending to be me, coming into my work and home.
Wait a minute, what's the situation?
A total stranger is pretending to be you
Does that mean? no…
It's not like I don't know anyone at all...
As a boss at work... how do the people around you react?
The people around me also thought that person was me...
Sigh...
Please believe! Please do something!
He's going crazy, arrest him and talk to him...
Okay, okay, calm down.
Please, please have a seat.Haha, please.
First of all, can I get your name?
This is Masaki Igawa (Watanabe) Masaki Igawa Yes.
What is your address? Morinuma-cho 150-7
150... Ah, Nexttown? yes
Ah ⚟📱
Ah... excuse me for a moment
Yes, hello, I'm Watanabe.
Yes, there is a person named Masaki Igawa.
yes yes
When someone pretends to be you and enters your home
Yes, I understand.
Could you please wait a moment?
The person in charge from the main office is on the way now.
So, if you could tell me more about it in detail.
got it
Thank you very much if you like.
♬〜
(car running sound)
(Watanabe) Huh? already?
♬〜
(Sound of car door opening and closing)
(Watanabe) Ugh! (Electric sound)
Ah, ah!
(Tada) It hurts!
♬〜
Hey…
(Tada) Ah!
(Tada) Huh?
Shit!
♬〜
Ah, it's Igawa. Please help me... Please help me.
Mr. Igawa
♬〜
Excuse me, please ride.
OK?
What happened?
I was attacked by someone pretending to be me.
Huh?
I tried to talk to the police.
Then I followed you there...
A police officer was also attacked...
I don't know what's going on...
Sorry, I can't think of anyone else to rely on.
(Sound of car door opening and closing)
(car lock sound)
I'm really sorry, no, please don't worry about it.
If you don't have ID, you can also go to internet cafes.
I can't stay the night.
Ah, it's not that tidy than that.
Sorry, no...
Please excuse me.
Um... please don't be surprised, eh?
There's something I want you to see
♬〜
It's my husband
I was really surprised to see you at the hospital.
I wonder if I'm seeing ghosts, but I don't have any spiritual sensations.
Why is your husband...
I had an accident two years ago...
I was a police officer
While inspecting the accident scene
Looks like a truck hit me...
♬〜
"ah…"
"(cry)"
The body was badly damaged...
I don't really remember the last time I saw my husband's face.
♬〜
They really look alike.
Haven't you heard that he has a brother?
Oh no...
You know, it's common in Korean dramas, isn't it?
Twins who were separated at birth
Like my brother? Maybe my younger brother
No, it doesn't matter... Ah, you're right, sorry.
No, something like this...
Was there anyone else involved?
Both of your parents are already...
I'm sorry, no.
If you are from the same university, do you have contact information?
I think it was on my phone, but I lost it...
Ah...
Do you know the name? I might be on SNS or something.
Ichihara…
What kind of character is Ryogo Ichihara?
At the market "ichi"... and Ryogo... that's it.
yes
Several people came out. Can you tell which ones?
Ah, sorry no...
It smells a bit, right? No, not at all.
Sorry
Can I change your clothes if you like? ah…
I still have my husband's.
♬〜
(birds chirping)
(sound of door opening)
Sorry I'm late because the police asked me a lot of questions.
(Mayumi) Who is that person? Looks like I ran away
(Mayumi) Ah...
If that man comes again, please contact me immediately.
don't believe what that guy says
♬〜
(sound of breathing)
(sound of door opening)
I'm sorry, but I thought you had a husband...
ah…
The clothes are perfect too
Ah yes
Ah, I found it when I narrowed it down by university name.
I really stayed in college.
I graduated in 4 years and immediately got a job.
Ichihara went to the hospital and stayed at the university.
You said you were going to become a researcher.
Do you want to go to university? I have tomorrow off.
Is it okay? yes
♬〜
(cry)
Ah... good morning
Ah, good morning. Ah, good morning.
yeah?
Ah... I look just like my dad, but he's not my dad.
Sorry, I was surprised.
Ah... it's Masaki Igawa.
Look, Kento also greets Mr. Igawa.
Haha...
♬〜
Dad hated cucumbers
Ah, that's right
♬〜
Eh... I'm kind of sorry.
Kento, if you don't go now, you'll be late for school.
Look, yes
Let's go, okay, take it.
Okay, let's go, yes, go, go, go.
(Kento) I'm coming, please come.
Be careful
Ah, sorry, ah, no.
How old are you?
I'm 6 years old. I was a daddy's boy.
I've been like this since my husband died.
Don't you have children?
Yes, sorry
I heard that you were trespassing. No, please don't worry about it.
(car unlock sound)
♬〜
I'll be waiting in the car, thank you.
(knock)
(Ichihara) Please
Ah, it’s been a while
Huh?
Um... which one are you?
Huh... I worked with Professor Masaki Igawa in Akao's laboratory.
Yichuan?
Ah... well, I haven't kept in touch with you at all since I graduated.
(Ichihara) Ah... I'm sorry, I don't remember that name.
Were you in sync?
We also took quantum mechanics class at the same time.
Ah... it's the wrong person... no, it's not.
After all, we studied here together.
Oh... no, look
When I said I was job-hunting, I stayed at university with you.
Would you like to do some research? That's what he said
Huh? So... oh yeah
You said you didn't want to get a job.
I got a job offer from Masano Tech, which I took as a souvenir.
Ichihara: You were in trouble.
Fufufufufu I remembered
And for some reason, I was the one who called to decline the offer.
Hey, Izakaya in front of the station
Haha, did you remember?
Who are you?
(Ichihara) Are you an acquaintance of Okazaki? Don't be silly
Huh? (Ichihara) Please come out.
♬〜
(Male)《Okay, I'll take a picture》
《Yes cheese》
♬〜
(Ichihara)《Are you an acquaintance of Okazaki? Who are you? 》
(Male)《Okay, I'll take a picture》
《Yes cheese》
《Yes, I will check it once》
♬〜
(Male) 《Okay, I'll take another photo then》
《Yes cheese》
♬〜
《Do you want to call it? 》 (Ichihara) 《Seriously? 》
《(Cough cough)》
《Ah, thank you for your help, my name is Ichihara.
Could you please connect me with the person in charge of recruitment? 》
(Ichihara)《Got it? Awesome》
《Sorry》
《I am very happy to have received the job offer...》
《Yes, please decline this time》
"yes…"
♬〜
Did you understand anything?
Mr. Igawa?
That was wrong... Huh?
All my memories from my university days...
all?
I joined the Akao lab because I was friends with Ichihara.
It wasn't me
What do you mean?
He was Fumiya Okazaki, a person I didn't know at all.
Why do you think someone else's life is yours?
(sigh)
Maybe there's something wrong with me after all.
no one remembers me
So who am I?
♬〜
Mr. Igawa Let's find more people who remember Mr. Igawa.
《Give it》 《What? Is that okay? 》
(Hanae)《Don't forget you》
(Ichihara) Ah, this is Ichihara from Sobu University.
📱(Tada) Did you show up? Yes.
(Tada) We apologize for the inconvenience.
📱(Ichihara) No, that...
Why does that person think he's Okazaki?
He seems a little confused after hitting his head in an accident.
I won't be visiting you again.
Oh wait... please wait
Okazaki was a close friend, so that person was Okazaki.
Please tell me what the relationship was.
📱(Tada) You don't need to know that.
Sorry to bother you
Mr. Shigeta! How are you doing?
I'm really good! Mr. Shigeta!
♬〜
(knock)
yes
(Tsumura) May I talk to you for a moment? (Ichihara) Well...
♬〜
(lock release sound)
(Rie) Did you feel comfortable in the bath?
(Male) It was hot today so I felt refreshed.
Oh really? It was good
♬〜
(sound of door opening)
(Rie) Did you feel comfortable in the bath?
(Male) It was hot today so I felt refreshed.
♬〜
(sound of door opening)
Ah... Mr. Isomura...
Hello
Ah! Mr. Isomura Mr. Isomura! This isn't a toilet.
Oh, excuse me, let's go to the bathroom.
(Isomura) Yes, this is it.
Because that's it
(Hanae) Combine this with this... Yeah.
Which one?
Mr. Tsukamoto
It's me, Igawa.
this…
Don't you remember?
Ikawa-kun?
what happened? I haven't seen you lately
I thought you had already quit
Oh no...
I'm just taking a little break
Don't worry (Hanae) That's good, hehehe
Are you using this?
yeah?
this
(Mayumi)《Even if you hate me so much that you want to forget about me
I'll put this here so I don't forget.
Mayumi-san, how are you doing?
Since it's your precious day off, go on a trip with Mayumi.
You also remembered Mayumi.
(Hanae) Of course hehehehehe nice photo hehehehe
(Mayumi)《Aaah, amazing! 》 《Aaah, amazing》
《Like》 《It's a nice place》
(Mayumi)《Yeah, ah, hey, let's take a photo》
《Okay》
《Let's go, yes cheese》
♬〜
(Hanae) Hehe
Ah... that wasn't a lie...
♬〜
That's a lie...
Masaki Igawa apparently talked about the career of another person named Fumiya Okazaki.
What do you mean? For what?
I don't know, but I heard that Igawa was in a state of confusion.
📱Let's find out a little more about what happened to Igawa.
Tsumura-kun, you have no relationship with Masaki Igawa.
📱From now on, take time for yourself
good?
got it
(knock)
Who were you talking to?
Are you Tsumura-san?
I think it's best not to have anything to do with that person anymore.
Are you friends? (Tsujimoto) It's a long time ago.
that person killed someone
should not be tolerated for any reason
♬〜
Mayumi (Mayumi) Kya!
Wait, wait, wait! Mayumi!
(Mayumi) Please stop it! Listen to me!
I'll call the police.
this
Don't you remember?
Shonan Kaigan Park visited by two people
When I took this picture...
Hey, buy your favorite strawberry soft serve ice cream.
But Mayumi is slow at eating.
I was melting into a mess and was about to cry...
(Mayumi)《Ah... Oh no no no no no no no! 》
"what? what? 》 (Mayumi)《Dangerous》
《Ah, ah, ah, ah, it's spilling so much》
(Mayumi) 《Wait a minute...》 《Eh, it's all muddy.》
Hehe, I was laughing when a dragon came along.
Take all my hot dogs and now I'm about to cry
♬〜
It's all just an insignificant event
For me, these are irreplaceable memories with Mayumi.
It's an important memory that I can't forget.
♬〜
I don't care who you are
i love mayumi
That's enough
Hey, it's dangerous to stay here.
Let's live together somewhere else
Mayumi!
♬〜
let's go
Ah...
(Electric sound)
♬〜
♬Let's go home Let's go home
(cry)
♬(Humming “Hi Ho”)
♬Let's go home Let's go home I'm hungry
(Female) I've been forgetting things a lot lately.
(Watanabe) Ah, forgetfulness? (Female) Yeah
(Watanabe) By the way, what did you eat last night?
(Female) Did the policeman eat fish yesterday?
(Watanabe) Yeah, I... Huh? What did you eat?
♬(Humming “Hi Ho”)
♬Let's go home Let's go home I'm hungry
♬Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home
♬Let's go home Let's go home
(Mitsuru/Takako) Hello, thank you.
(Takako) Are you back from work? Yeah
(Mitsuru) Thank you for your hard work, Mr. Sudo.
Thank you for your hard work. Every day is amazing.
I walk 10,000 steps every day! amazing
That's too much
It's about 6,000 steps, but 10,000 steps is fine.
In that case, 5000 steps would be fine.
Why say less? But 70% more is terrible.
When I think back on it later
From "Ah, I walked 6,000 steps every day"
“I walked 10,000 steps” feels better, right?
What do you think?
Remember that lie, what should I do? Well, well, well, well, well.
Please do your best today too
Yes, thank you
Most of the time, it's too much.
(Takako) What do you mean by being too excited? (Mitsuru) Your voice is so loud.
(Takako) Your voice is so loud. (Mitsuru) You got angry, right? The other day
I'm home
(Mayumi) Welcome back
♬〜
I forgot to buy Peter's snack.
Sorry Peter
Which one are you? Huh?
Is it so easy for people's memories to disappear?
Kya! (Kousaka) For you
I want you to start a new life
I don't have that kind of thing when I kill someone.
Mr. Igawa! (Mayumi) Do you know each other?
No... again, memories I don't know are floating in my head.
I have a story to tell... Mr. Igawa.